var quiz =[{"answers": ["Some may be willing to pay for clean air, but do not have the money.", "Green products can never be green.", "If economic systems created the environmental problems, how can they solve them?", "Green products cost more and not everyone can afford them."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a critique of market environmentalism?"}, {"answers": ["greenwashing", "cap and trade", "banking programs", "green taxes"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "If my factory installs super-efficient smokestacks that cause my air pollution emissions to drastically drop, I can take advantage of which program to make extra money?"}, {"answers": ["both an increase in supply and a decrease in demand.", "increase in demand", "decrease in demand", "increase in supply"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "According to the market response model, innovations can lead to what?"}, {"answers": ["monopsony", "monopoly", "transaction costs", "externalities"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "The type of market failure in which the costs or benefits of an activity to a third party are not figured into the activitys cost is known as what?"}, {"answers": ["greenwashing", "green taxes", "green consumption", "green banking programs"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Consumer-driven environmental change can be achieved through which one of the following methods?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "More efficient use of a resource can lead to increased consumption of that resource."}, {"answers": ["Standards used for certification", "Negative association with greenwashing", "Verification process", "Cost and affordability"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is not a problem associated with green certification for companies?"}, {"answers": ["banking programs", "green taxes", "cap and trade", "green consumerism"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Wetland development in one place to make up for wetland destruction in another location is an example of what policy?"}, {"answers": ["They tend to be apolitical.", "They accurately attribute value to complex and dynamic ecological systems.", "They exclude participation of future generations.", "They are accessible for poor and marginalized people."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following statements about market-based solutions is true?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Many companies spend more on trying to make their products appear \u201cgreener\u201d than actually being green."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Market-based solutions are always equitable."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "It is possible to include everyone in the bargaining process that might be affected by environmental problems."}, {"answers": ["Jevons\u2019 Paradox", "Market Response Model", "Coase Theorem", "Externalities"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is used to describe the observation that more efficient use of a resource can lead to greater environmental degradation?"}, {"answers": ["Hawk Mountain", "green taxes", "Paul J. Rainey Sanctuary", "green consumption"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of a market solution that provides personal gain as well as environmental prosperity?"}, {"answers": ["To encourage use of the item being taxed.", "To decrease the use of the item being taxed, and drive innovation and substitution for it.", "To combat government inefficiencies over the regulation of the item being taxed.", "Increase demand for the item being taxed."], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "What is the purpose of using green taxes?"}, {"answers": ["Green Seal Certified", "USDA Organic", "Energy Star", "U.S. Green Housing Council"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which of the following logos or groups is NOT an actual green certification?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Banking programs require significant regulatory intervention."}, {"answers": ["states that optimal distribution of goods will occur as long as property rights are clearly defined.", "explains the impact of affluence on the environment.", "describes how conservation efforts of materials actually leads to increased use.", "asserts that population expands geometrically, but resources increase arithmetically."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The Coase theorem:"}, {"answers": ["Addressing how much pollution should be allowed requires tradeoffs and regulatory experience.", "Doesn\u2019t consider the local effects of concentrated pollution.", "A black market has been created to deal with environmental trading.", "Often excludes many with interests in reducing pollution."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a problem with cap and trade policies?"}, {"answers": ["monopoly", "externalities", "monopsony", "individual consumerism"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "When you have one buyer for many sellers what is this called?"}, {"answers": ["decreased consumption", "greenwashing", "increased conservation", "contracts and bargaining"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "According to the Coase theorem, the key to controlling externalities is what?"}, {"answers": ["are negligible.", "the most important causes of environmental degradation.", "mediated by innovation.", "the single largest source of problems for the environment."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The outcome of the wager between Ehrlich and Simon suggested that the effects of population growth on the environment are:"}, {"answers": ["New York", "Michigan", "California", "Hawaii"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "According to your notes, which of the following states has the highest gasoline tax rate?"}, {"answers": ["green taxes", "green certification", "greenwashing", "green consumption"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which of\u00a0 the following relies on consumer demand to change environmental conditions?"}, {"answers": ["greenwashing", "cap and trade", "green consumption", "banking programs"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "A market-based solution to environmental problems in which a pollution limit is set and permits to pollute may be bought and sold on a free market in known as what?"}, {"answers": ["purchasing recycled paper", "banning indirect taxes on gasoline", "purchasing a fishing license", "banking excess water for later use"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a market-based solution to environmental problems?"}, {"answers": ["monopolies", "transaction costs", "greenwashing", "externalities"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which of the following is NOT an example of market failure?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Greenwashing is the attempt by corporations to accurately report their environmentally-friendly practices."}, {"answers": ["It is a process, not a final solution to environmental problems.", "It assumes there are no transaction costs for bargaining and contracts.", "It assumes that property rights are exclusive.", "It relies on a growing population to create solutions for environmental problems."], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "Which of the following is NOT a problem associated with the Coase Theorem and free-market environmentalism?"}, {"answers": ["externalities", "greenwashing", "government intervention", "market failures"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "What term refers to what occurs when there is a mismatch between economic theory and the real-world?"}]

quizCollection['3'] = quiz

if (debug) {
  console.log("Finished loading Quiz 3")
}
